说话人1: 你说当我们传递一个函数或者传递一个函数定义时,
&gt;&gt; Speaker 1: You say when we're passing a
function or passing a function definition,
这也是一个函数引用吗？
is that also just like
a function reference?
因为你不能改变它，它已经在内存中了？
Because you can't change it and
it's already in memory?
威尔 · 森特斯: 是的，所以我决定是否
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Yeah, so
I was deciding whether or
不包括我的额外奖励。
not to include my little bonus piece.
我们就这么简单吧。
Let's just keep it as simple as this.
全局中的这个数组保存在全局中。
This array here in global
is saved in global.
然后将其解析为一个链接，返回到它保存在全局中的位置。
It is then parsed in as a link back
to where it was saved in global.
现在我拯救全球，没有一个标签。
Now I was saving global without a label.
它只是存在于全局中，但我们实际上解析了它的一个链接。
It was just there in global, but
we actually parse in a link to it.
我们不会抄袭它。
We are not copying it in.
我们正在解析，是的，一个关于它最初保存在全局内存中的位置的引用。
We're parsing, yes, a reference to where
it was initially saved in global memory.
如果你还记得我们传入数组的早期版本，我们保存了1,
If you remember our earlier version where
we passed in my array, we saved that 1,
2,3个数组，然后我们传回一个链接。
2, 3 array in global, and
then we just passed a link back to it.
这就是为什么我们不想改变复制数组的内部
And that's why we don't want to
change inside of copy array and
操作我们传入的数据，因为这会改变全局数据,
manipulate the data we pass in because
that would be changing the global data,
没有功能就很难预测会发生什么。
which is hard to predict what's
then gonna happen without function.
他们称之为副作用。
They call it a side effect.
但是，在这里，我们创建一个全新的数组，每个单独的元素,
But instead, here, we create a brand new
array, and take each individual element,
插入新的阵列。
stick it in that new array.
我们的输入数组保持不变，保持不变。
And our input array stays unmutated,
stays unchanged.
很好，丹，是的，继续，丹。
Nice, by Dan, yeah, go ahead, Dan.
但是这个函数，你可以称它为函数引用，或者
&gt;&gt; Dan: But the function,
can you call it a function reference, or
这是一个函数定义吗? ——威尔 · 森特斯: 我明白了,
is it a function definite-
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: I see,
是啊，我们又来了，一样的事情。
yeah, we're again, same thing here.
就我们的功能来说,
With our function, again,
这是一个返回原始保存的 multilyby2函数的链接。
it's a link back to the original
saved multiplyBy2 function.
因此，任何函数、数组或对象，当它被保存时,
So any function, array, or
object, when it's saved,
如果我们在其他地方使用它
if we ever use it anywhere else and
链接到它，我们实际上引用了它的原始保存版本。
link to it, we're actually referring
back to its original saved version.
Dan 说得很好，太好了。
Very nice from Dan, excellent.
彼得? 彼得: 有点像幕后工作
Peter?
&gt;&gt; Peter: Kind of a behind the scenes
当 for 循环运行时，它是否有自己的执行上下文？
thing, when the for loop is running, does
it kind of get its own execution context?
威尔 · 森坦斯: 不，它有自己受保护的名称空间。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: No,
it gets its own protected namespace.
也就是说如果我们用 let 来定义 i,
That is to say that if we
use let to define the i,
我只能在那个区块范围内，也就是那个小花括号里。
that i is only available inside that block
scope, which is the little curly braces.
但是它不是一个执行，它不是把它放在调用堆栈上。
But it is not an execution it is
not putting that on the call stack.
它只是内存中另一个被标记名称的受保护空间。
It's just another protected space
in memory for those labeled names.
好吧问得好。
Okay, yeah, yeah, nice question.